{
    "id": "7db91adde9034d148aed1cae122bf439",
    "title": "Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………. finished the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "am"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f21726506d5d45999692ef13dc1ad194"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ……………….. your lunch?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eat",
                "ate",
                "eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bd70086da84e4af5a14f79fd4f896f5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has not return",
                "is not returned",
                "has not returned"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6bc3e2c531f14cf9869539046ebd491e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… such a mess.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never saw",
                "have never seen",
                "have never saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eda9ef1017784d8e8cc176f13071494c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. he brought his violin?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Is",
                "Has",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f724dc109aed4861b59f659484c1e298"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever …………………. to Australia?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "being",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ca4e188c0aba4018bfe9d1237e103d7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… all the plays of Shakespeare.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "am read",
                "have read"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d9eb51ca00b84c659d86375d396f86aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents ...................... me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has never hurt",
                "have never hurt",
                "have never hurted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d5045e6d594f43b5a2807d3568cac197"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................... always wanted to be a soldier.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6168b1d6b2f8426089edeefcf3ba9700"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. to anybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never apologized",
                "has never apologized",
                "have never apologized"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "151172ad9dae48a5941187874337517a"
        }
    ]
}